

AHMAD FAUZAN

Mobile +6281398909066
LinkedIn @ahmadfauzaan613
Web Portofolio ahmad-fauzan.netlify.app
Email ahmadfauzaan613@gmail.com

SUMMARY

Has one year experience in the field of Front End Developer in working on several projects as a freelancer, and also as a Back End Developer for 6 months while using web frameworks such as Bootstrap, ReactJs, NodeJS(expressJS), Codelgniter (PHP), and (Gin Gonic) Golang. As an addition, has an experience on UI/UX Design by using Figma or Adobe XD that combines while doing the projects as an freelancer.

TOOLS

- Figma, Adobe XD
- HTML
- CSS (Bootsrap, Sass)
- JavaScript(ReactJs)
- Golang
- PHP (CodeIgniter)
- Git, Github
- VS Code
- Postman

HIGHLIGHTED SKILLS

- implementing UI design on the website
- Familiar with Web Architecture starting from code structure, separating and storing certain files, etc
- Has a good track record of team work & time management
- Always update with new technology and trends
- Has ability to solve existing problems or bugs
- Has strong intention and commitment to work as professional programmer

EDUCATION HISTORY

INFORMATION SYSTEM
Gunadarma University | 2016 - 2021

EXPERIENCE

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

Assist.id | 25 June 2021 - 25 July 2021

- Use JavaScript and ReactJS as the framework

BACK END DEVELOPER

Assist.id | 21 April 2021 - 21 June 2021

- Use NodeJs and Loopback, ExpressJS as the framework

BACK END DEVELOPER, PERSONAL PROJECT Aplikasi Investasi UMKM | Oct 2020 - Des 2020

- Develops an application that can be used by all people who want to start their business ideas or become an investors
- Use Golang programming language as the backend
- Implement the project using VS Code and Postman

BACK END DEVELOPER, INTERNSHIP DLI EDU VENTURE | June 2020 - Sept 2020

- Using CMS to build a dynamic web
- Work collaboratively with the team to develop web admin, user login, and register user
- Use PHP programming language and CI as the framework
- Fix bugs that were arise in the web